copper?
どう?
good.
うまい
Wait, is this okay?
ちょっと、これ、いい?
One more bite.
もう一口
Yeah.
うん
But I'm probably not cute.
でも、僕、多分、かわしくはない
Yeah.
うん
It's not cute.
かわしくはない
It doesn't matter.
かわない
That's right.
だよね
Good, but.
うまい、でも
It's warm.
あったかくて
I want to try some of this crepe.
こっちのクレープの方は、ちょっと食べたい
Like this crepe.
こっちのクレープとか
It might be sweet.
甘いかもね
Oh, wait.
あ、ちょっと
Are you inviting me?
誘ってますか?
I'll invite you.
誘っちゃいますよ
I got really excited.
ギンギンになっちゃいました
You're fine.
元気だね
It's cute again.
かわいくなったね、また
thank you.
ありがとう
Hey, what's wrong?
ねぇ、どうしたの?
What did you eat yesterday?
昨日何食べたの?
Yesterday was bean sprouts.
昨日は、もやし
Bean sprouts?
もやし?
I'm living a modest life.
ひもじ生活してる
No, I like it.
違う、好きなの
Do you like bean sprouts?
もやしが好きなの?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
That's quite a saving.
結構、節約化なんだね
Yeah, it's cheap.
うん、安い
Do you like sweets?
スイーツとか好き?
Yeah.
うん
like?
好 き?
What do you like?
何が好き?
I like pretty much anything as long as it's sweet.
甘いのだったら、比較的何でも好き
for example?
例えば?
I like macarons.
マカロンとか好きだよ
It looks like a macaron.
マカロンっぽい顔してるもんね
Does it hurt to gain weight?
太ったって痛い?
not at all.
全然
You've lost weight, actually.
痩せたっしょ、むしろ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
I narrowed it down a bit.
ちょっと絞った
They have delicious crepes.
美味しいクレープあるからさ
eat?
食べる?
eat.
食べる
Do you say cutely that you want to eat crepes?
クレープ食べたいって可愛く言うの?
I want to eat crepe.
クレープ食べたい
picture?
え?
what?
何?
I want to eat crepe.
クレープ食べたい
Now, the sound of the car is drowning out everything.
今、車の音にかき消されて全然
It's here though.
ここなんだけど
Hooraho hora.
ほ らほらほら
Have a look?
見てみ?
It's so delicious.
すげえ美味しいんだよ
A lot of things happened.
色々あって
Are you making it?
作ってんの?
Yeah.
うん
what up?
どうした?
I felt a little happy.
ちょっと嬉しいなって思った
happy?
嬉しい?
What?
何が?
I'm laughing because I love you so much.
すげえ好きだから笑ってるじゃん
It's kind of girly.
なんかガーリーだね
Ah, it rang.
あ、鳴った
It rang, so wait a minute.
鳴ったからちょっとほら
Looks delicious, right?
美味しそうでしょ
looks delicious.
美味しそう
Let's eat, then.
食べよっか、じゃあ
oh.
おー
Smaller than my face.
顔よりちっちゃい
Isn't it big?
おっきいんじゃない?
that.
それ
Is it smaller than your face?
顔 よりちっちゃいの?
LOL Isn't it bigger than your face?
笑 顔よりさ、 おっきいんじゃない?
that.
それ
Because my face is small.
顔ちっちゃいから
Warm.
あったかい
hot.
熱い
hot?
熱い?
What were you doing?
あれ、 何してたんだっけ?
work.
仕事
work model.
仕事モデル
That's right.
そうだよね
I guess they sold beer or something?
なんかビールとか売ってたんじゃない?
oh yeah.
そうそう
That was a while ago.
それはもうちょっと前
A while ago.
ちょっと前
Wouldn't it be nice to have a crepe shop?
クレープ屋さんとかもいいんじゃない?
Does it suit you?
似合う?
You can eat it.
食べていいよ
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
Did it have bean sprout topping on it?
それ、もやしトッピングしたの?
different.
違う
salted caramel.
塩キャラメル
Not salted caramel bean sprouts.
塩キャラメルもやしじゃなくて
It looks delicious though.
美味しそうだけど
It's delicious, isn't it?
美味しくていいだろ
Ah, it's normal. Ah, it's going to bite you there.
あ、 普通に あ、 あそこかぶりつくね
Fogging.
かぶり
It's biting into me.
かぶりついたね
delicious.
美味しい
please.
どうぞ
It's crispy and delicious.
サ クサクしてて美味しい
It's crispy.
サクサクしてるんだ
That's nice.
いいな
eat?
食べる?
Ah, that was kind of cute just now.
あ、今のちょっと可愛かった
Can I have it again?
もう一回もらってもいい?
May I?
いいですか?
Oh.
あーって
May I?
いいですか?
Awesome.
すげえ
i want to eat.
食べたい
There's only skin.
皮しかない
All I have is the skin.
皮しかないんだけど
But it's delicious.
でも、ちゃんと美味しいよ
It's delicious.
ちゃんと美味しいよ
I only eat the skin.
皮しか食べてないけど
I want to lift it up.
上に持ち上げたいんだ
The contents haven't come out yet.
中身出てきてないでしょ、まだ
But it's delicious.
でも、美味い
Fluffy.
ふわふわ
But it's bad.
でも、悪い
It's as fluffy as your cheeks.
ほ っぺったぐらいふわふわ
I don't want to eat, but I don't want to eat.
食べたくないけど、 食べたくない
I like it, you look cute today too.
いいね、今日もなんか可愛い
Today too.
今日 も
I see.
なるほど
I can see it.
見えちゃう
picture?
え?
Can't you see it?
見えちゃうんじゃない?
Many points.
多 分
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
I'm worried.
心配してる
I probably won't eat this cheese.
このチーズは多分食べない
Can't eat?
食べれない?
I want to eat it.
食べたいな
Is it okay to eat this?
これ、よく食べていい?
copper?
どう?
delicious.
美味い
Is this good?
これ、いい?
One more thing.
もう一つ
Maybe you should buy it.
多分、買わせたまえ
Yeah.
うん
cute.
可愛い
可愛 い
Delicious, though.
美味い、でも
It's warm.
温かくて
I want to eat this crepe.
こっちのクレープの方は、 食べ たい
Like this crepe.
こっちのクレープとか
It might be sweet.
甘いかもね
Oh, wait.
あ、ちょっと
Are you inviting me?
誘ってますか?
I'll invite you.
誘っちゃいますよ
yeah?
ん?
I got really excited.
ギンギンになっちゃいました
You're fine.
元気だね
When I wanted to buy it, it was already sold out.
俺、買おうと思ったらもう、 売り切れてたわ
That's the end.
それで最後
picture?
え?
Hey, it's on.
ちょっと、ついてる
Here.
ここに
It's on.
ついてる
Which one?
どっち?
picture?
え?
Over there.
あそこで
Erotic.
エロい
sweet.
甘い
I just can't stand it.
ちょっと、我慢できないから
Wait a minute, let's go.
ちょっと、行こう
Because I can't stand it.
我慢できないから
Where are you going?
どこへ行くの?
Hey, dreamland.
ちょっと、夢の国
You like it, right?
好きでしょ
Do you like it?
好きかな?
I don't like girls.
女子は好きじゃん
dreamland.
夢の国
I wonder why I like it, everyone.
なんで好きなんだろうね、みんな
Because it's a dream.
夢だから
Because it's a dream?
夢だから?
After all, I want to go to my dreams.
やっぱ、夢に行きたい
Hey, I've got a ticket to dreamland.
ちょっと、夢の国のチケット取ってるから
Let's go together.
一緒に行こうぜ
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみにしてる
From the day of the exam.
試験日からね
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
It's just a little bit more.
もうちょっとだから
You can eat it.
食べていいよ
It's delicious, isn't it?
美味しいでしょ
Because there's something more delicious.
もっと美味しいものがあるから
my crepe
俺のクレープ
There's my crepe.
俺のクレープあるから
Eat.
食べて
nice to meet you.
初めまして
what?
何?
誰?
friend.
友達
Because I'm a camera kid.
カメラ小僧だから
thank you.
よろしくお願いします
I guess I'm used to it.
や っぱ慣れてるね
I'm used to being photographed.
撮られ慣れてるからね
Work pattern?
仕事柄?
Work pattern.
仕事柄
Do you work as a model?
モデルとかやってるのね
still.
まだ
still?
まだ?
What kind of work do you do these days?
最近はどんな仕事?
The salary itself is lower than before.
前よりは給料自体は下がっちゃってる
Because I'm still new.
まだ新人だから
It's no good if it doesn't sell.
売れてないとダメ
TV or something.
テレビとか
Do you run a magazine or something?
雑誌とかやってるの?
Maybe even a magazine.
雑誌までもいいかも
Feels like a near-idol.
近アイドルみたいな感じ
I don't appear in everyday life.
日常に出らない
It's like selling beer today.
今日はビールを売るときみたいな
My life was selling beer when I was selling it.
ビール売ってた頃の生活は売ってます
My skin is really moist, though.
お肌すごい潤ってますけどね
That's a bit...
そこはちょっと...
I just asked him what he ate yesterday, and he said he ate bean sprouts.
さっき昨日何食べたって聞いたら もやし食べたって
Because I don't have much money.
ちょっとお金ないから
I'm saving money.
節約してる
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Are you saving money?
節約してるの?
It's like he's clutching an amazing clip and won't let go.
すごいクリップ握りしめて 離さないみたいな
Have a proper meal.
ちゃんとした食事がね
Oh, because there isn't.
あ、ないからね
Instead of a meal.
食事代わりに
Meal replacement.
食事代わり
Please eat it.
食べてもらって
Did it get a little cold?
ちょっと冷めちゃったかな?
The ingredients have finally come out, haven't they?
やっと具が出てきたんじゃないですか
It's a clip...it's a bit like a commercial.
クリップの...ちょっとクリップのさ なんかCMさ みたいに
I almost finished eating.
さ めっちゃ食べかけ
CM pool CM pool?
CMプール CMプール?
I don't know.
わかんない
Eat cutely and lick your lips
可愛く食べて ペロってして 唇を
That's good.
いい っすね
delicious.
美味しい
Shall we eat together?
一緒に食べる?
Ah, that's good.
あ、いいっすね
It's really good.
め ちゃくちゃいいっすね
It's very difficult.
めちゃ難しい
I want it.
欲しがっちゃうな
Can I have the current series?
今の一連の もらっていいですか?
It's going to stick together.
くっついちゃうの
series of current series
一連の 今の一連の
A little bit of a high-level, high-level world, a little bit of a temptation, a little bit of a temptation
ちょっと 上目 上 目の世界で ちょっと誘惑 誘惑しつつ
So cute, so cute Eat, eat, eat, eat
可愛 い めちゃくちゃ可愛い 食べて 食べて 食べて 食べて
Please, can I eat it?
っていう お願い 食べていいの?
Oh, it hurts.
あ、痛い
Ah ha ha ha ha I guess you can let me eat too, okay?
あ はは はは ちょっと俺も 俺も食べさせていいじゃん?
Do you eat in such a naughty way?
こんなエッチな 食べ方するの?
delicious.
美味しい
I feel like it's grape.
グレープな気がする
I feel like it's grapey.
グレープな気がするよ
Have you done anything naughty recently?
最近やらしいことしたの?
I haven't.
してない
Let's do it.
しようじゃん
That's some really naughty underwear.
すっごいやらしい下着だね
Are you wearing these naughty pants?
こんなやらしいパンツ 履いてるの?
ERROR
こんなやらしいの履いて グレープ食べてたの?
I'm beautiful too.
私も綺麗なんですけど
Me too.
私もはい
It smells good.
いい匂いですよ
That's no good.
ダメだろ
Because it's beautiful.
綺麗なんだから
It's very thin.
すごく薄い
Isn't it?
じゃねーか
No, no, no.
いやいや、やば
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
I'll take it home.
持って帰るね
A lot came out.
いっぱい出てきたね
There will be a lot of it.
すっごいいっぱい出るね
Under me too.
俺の下にも
Shake your butt.
お尻ふりふりして
cute.
かわいい
That's a nice butt.
いいお尻だね
copper?
どう?
Are you going to spend your time smelling naughty?
やらしい匂いを過ごすの?
Leave it alone for a while and go to sleep.
ちょっとおけおけ、寝てやねん
It bit into me.
食い込んじゃった
It bit me in.
食い込んじゃったよ
Aren't you going here too?
こっちも行ってこない?
That's naughty.
やらしいね
My butt hole is twitching.
お尻の穴ひくひくしてる
You know, it made me twitch.
ほ ら、ひくひくさせたよ
I'm twitching.
ひくひくしてるよ
Okay.
よし
No way.
いやー
I'll take this home.
これ持って帰るね
Just a little bit,
ちょっとさ、
Let's have a look.
見て もらおうよ
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
That's fine.
いいじゃん
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
No, no.
やだやだ
A man is peeking out from a tower apartment.
タワーマンションから 男が覗いてるよ
I can't see it.
見えない
I'm sleeping a lot.
すごい寝てる
You like being seen, right?
見られるの好きでしょ?
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
Hey, you like it, don't you?
ほ ら、好きでしょ?
Let me take a look.
見てもらおうよ
Let's take a look.
見て も ら お う よ
Look.
ほ ら
That's naughty.
やらしい
Look outside.
ほら、外見て
Properly.
ちゃんと
Is anyone watching?
誰か見てる?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
feeling
気持
Is it okay?
ち いい?
Look, outside.
ほら、外
From that pansion.
あそこの パンションから
Hey.
ねえ
It's amazing.
すごいですよ
Those are beautiful feet.
きれいな足だね
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
copper?
どう?
Look this way.
こっち向いて
It's completely visible from below.
すっごい下から丸見えだよ
That's amazing.
すっごいね
full.
いっぱい
Did you see a nice face?
いい顔見えちゃった?
It looks fine.
上手く見えちゃうよ
beautiful.
きれい
It's okay because you're my older sister, right?
お姉さんだから大丈夫でしょ?
Are you going to take a photo like this?
こういう撮影するでしょ?
Such a beautiful color.
すっごいきれいな色
Look, twitch.
ほら、ひくひくして
Ru.
る
Open it yourself, chan.
自 分でさ、 開いてね、ちゃん
Open it yourself and show me.
自分で開いてよく見せて
Open it yourself?
自分で開く?
yes.
そう
Here you go, yourself.
ほら、自分で
I'll put it away like this.
こうしまうよ